philadelphiapass.com 2019-06-23

# Customer Care Center 1-800-887-9103

What information we collect from you

In General: Smart Destinations Inc. only collects personal information that you voluntarily provide to us. This includes personal information that can be used to identify you such as name, address, phone number, e-mail address and billing information (credit card number, cardholder name and expiration date).

No personal information is required to access any area of our website and is collected only to complete your purchase transaction. 

Automatic Information. We automatically collect some information about your computer when you visit Smartdestinations.com. For example, we will collect your IP address, Web browser software (such as Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer), and referring Web site. We also may collect information about your online activity, such as pages viewed and purchases made. One of our goals in collecting this automatic information is to improve user experience. 

Cookies and Other Web Technologies. When you visit Smartdestinations.com, we may assign your computer a "cookie" (a small, unique identifier text file). This data cannot be used to identify any visitor individually. We use cookies to track what pages you have viewed so that we can learn how to make our site as efficient as possible. We also use cookies to collect anonymous aggregate data for our attraction partners. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie, however you will not be able to purchase Smart Destinations products over the internet if your browser does not accept cookies. Our customer service team is standing by to support customers via phone, however, and can be reached at 800-887-9103. 

Information Collected by Third-Party Advertising Companies. Third-party advertisers, such as those we use to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet, may use cookies and other technologies (such as Web beacons or single-pixel GIFS) for several purposes, including: to measure the effectiveness of their ads; to analyze, modify, and personalize advertising content on Smartdestinations.com and other sites; and to provide ads about goods and services we hope will be of interest to you. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers are not covered by this Privacy Policy. You can find out more about third-party advertisers and explore the option of not having this information collected by visiting this website http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed 

How we use your information

Smartdestinations.com uses sensitive billing information (such as cardholder name, credit card number, and expiration date) for the purpose of completing the purchases you conduct on our site. We also provide this information to a third party to help us evaluate the fraud risk associated with the information that you provide. This third party maintains Level 1 PCI compliance which is the highest level that a party can achieve. We use other information about you for the following general purposes: to provide you with the products and services you request; to provide you with order confirmation and updates; to manage your account, including processing bills and providing notifications; to communicate with you in general; to respond to your questions and comments; to measure interest in and improve our products, services, and Web site; to notify you about special offers and products or services that may be of interest to you if you have opted to receive email, to solicit information from you, including through surveys; to resolve disputes, collect fees, or troubleshoot problems; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce our Terms of Use; and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection.

We only use your personal information to complete the transactions you have intentionally initiated. We use this information to confirm your order and to respond to any questions you may have. Where required, we also share this information with certain intermediaries (UPS and other shippers) strictly to process and ship your order. We NEVER sell or rent your personal information to any third party for marketing, commercial, or any other purpose that is not essential to complete these transactions. We will hold your personal information on our systems indefinitely or until you request it is deleted. Even if we delete your personal information it may persist on backup or archival media for legal, tax or regulatory purposes.

There may at some point be 'e-mail to a friend' features on our site that will allow you to easily share product or other valuable information with your friends. Any e-mails provided to us in the use of these features are used solely for direction of the e-mail communication. These e-mails are not retained in our database nor are they used for any other communication other than for the purpose they are originally solicited for.

**IMPORTANT** : For those customers that visited our website from a link on the following website www.nycgo.com , you may have certain information such as your email address and product purchased provided to the owner of that website and that email may be used by that owner for marketing purposes. You will still have the option at time of purchase or in the future to opt out of receiving future marketing emails.

For Canadian Residents: Your personal information may be processed and stored outside of the province in which you reside and/or outside of Canada, by Smart Destinations or by an affiliated or unaffiliated service provider, for the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement and, under the laws of these other jurisdictions, in certain circumstances foreign courts, law enforcement agencies or regulatory agencies may be entitled to access your personal information.

With whom we share your information
     Smart Destinations.com may release your information in the following situations: 

  * In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
  * When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of Smartdestinations.com, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Service and other agreements.
  * In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
  * Other than as set out above, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information.
  * We also may share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers and investors. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors a Web site receives or what are the most popular vacation destinations. This information does not contain any personal information and is used to develop content and services we hope you will find helpful and of interest.

How you can edit, update, correct or delete your information

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. When you make a purchase on the gocity.com site, you will be given a choice as to whether you want to receive e-mail messages from Leisure Pass Group Inc. If you wish to stop receiving emails, you may click the “Unsubscribe” link in any message to be unsubscribed. You may also let us know by calling 800-887-9103 or by sending us an email. Please be sure to note your email address, mailing address, full name, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. Unsubscribe can take up to 15 days. If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing address or other personal information with us please contact us the same way.

How we protect your information

We want you to feel confident about using Smart Destinations.com to plan and purchase your travel, so we are committed to protecting the information we collect. While no Web site can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us, including partnering with online industry leaders such as Verisign and HackerSafe. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they only may do so for permitted business functions. In addition, we use Secure Socket Layers (SSL) encryption when transmitting your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we employ firewalls and intrusion detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your information. If you wish for us to no longer retain your data and want it removed from our systems, please send a request to Customer Service. If you are unhappy with our privacy or data protection policies, please send a note to Customer Service.

Children's privacy

Smart Destinations.com takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. Our web sites are general audience sites. We take pains not to permit anyone under the age of 13 to register with us. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13 without their parent's consent.

Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's access to the web.

External Links

Our web site contains links to web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any personal information on such site.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our web site. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our web site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. This policy was posted in May 2018.
